row	col	id	content	tokens	lemmaTokens	posTags	nerTags	nerValues	number	date	num2	list	listId
-1	0	fb:row.row.year	Year	year	year	NN	DURATION						
-1	1	fb:row.row.film	Film	film	Film	NNP	O						
-1	2	fb:row.row.role	Role	role	role	NN	O						
-1	3	fb:row.row.language	Language	language	language	NN	O						
-1	4	fb:row.row.notes	Notes	notes	note	NNS	O						
0	0	fb:cell.2008	2008	2008	2008	CD	DATE	2008	2008.0	2008-xx-xx			
0	1	fb:cell.moggina_manasu	Moggina Manasu	moggina|manasu	Moggina|Manasu	NNP|NNP	PERSON|PERSON	|					
0	2	fb:cell.chanchala	Chanchala	chanchala	Chanchala	NNP	LOCATION						
0	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
0	4	fb:cell.filmfare_award_for_best_actress_kannada_karnataka_state_film_award_for_best_actress	Filmfare Award for Best Actress - Kannada\nKarnataka State Film Award for Best Actress	filmfare|award|for|best|actress|-|kannada|karnataka|state|film|award|for|best|actress	Filmfare|award|for|best|actress|-|Kannada|Karnataka|State|Film|award|for|best|actress	NNP|NN|IN|JJS|NN|:|NNP|NNP|NNP|NNP|NN|IN|JJS|NN	O|O|O|O|O|O|LOCATION|LOCATION|O|O|O|O|O|O	|||||||||||||				Filmfare Award for Best Actress - Kannada|Karnataka State Film Award for Best Actress	fb:part.filmfare_award_for_best_actress_kannada|fb:part.karnataka_state_film_award_for_best_actress
1	0	fb:cell.2009	2009	2009	2009	CD	DATE	2009	2009.0	2009-xx-xx			
1	1	fb:cell.olave_jeevana_lekkachaara	Olave Jeevana Lekkachaara	olave|jeevana|lekkachaara	Olave|Jeevana|Lekkachaara	NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|PERSON|PERSON	||					
1	2	fb:cell.rukmini	Rukmini	rukmini	Rukmini	NNP	PERSON						
1	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
1	4	fb:cell.innovative_film_award_for_best_actress	Innovative Film Award for Best Actress	innovative|film|award|for|best|actress	innovative|Film|award|for|best|actress	JJ|NNP|NN|IN|JJS|NN	O|O|O|O|O|O	|||||				Innovative Film Award for Best Actress	fb:part.innovative_film_award_for_best_actress
2	0	fb:cell.2009	2009	2009	2009	CD	DATE	2009	2009.0	2009-xx-xx			
2	1	fb:cell.love_guru	Love Guru	love|guru	love|guru	NN|NN	O|O	|					
2	2	fb:cell.kushi	Kushi	kushi	Kushi	NNP	PERSON						
2	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
2	4	fb:cell.filmfare_award_for_best_actress_kannada	Filmfare Award for Best Actress - Kannada	filmfare|award|for|best|actress|-|kannada	Filmfare|award|for|best|actress|-|Kannada	NNP|NN|IN|JJS|NN|:|NNP	O|O|O|O|O|O|LOCATION	||||||				Filmfare Award for Best Actress - Kannada	fb:part.filmfare_award_for_best_actress_kannada
3	0	fb:cell.2010	2010	2010	2010	CD	DATE	2010	2010.0	2010-xx-xx			
3	1	fb:cell.krishnan_love_story	Krishnan Love Story	krishnan|love|story	Krishnan|Love|Story	NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|PERSON|PERSON	||					
3	2	fb:cell.geetha	Geetha	geetha	Geetha	NNP	PERSON						
3	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
3	4	fb:cell.filmfare_award_for_best_actress_kannada_udaya_award_for_best_actress	Filmfare Award for Best Actress - Kannada\nUdaya Award for Best Actress	filmfare|award|for|best|actress|-|kannada|udaya|award|for|best|actress	Filmfare|award|for|best|actress|-|Kannada|Udaya|award|for|best|actress	NNP|NN|IN|JJS|NN|:|NNP|NNP|NN|IN|JJS|NN	O|O|O|O|O|O|LOCATION|O|O|O|O|O	|||||||||||				Filmfare Award for Best Actress - Kannada|Udaya Award for Best Actress	fb:part.filmfare_award_for_best_actress_kannada|fb:part.udaya_award_for_best_actress
4	0	fb:cell.2010	2010	2010	2010	CD	DATE	2010	2010.0	2010-xx-xx			
4	1	fb:cell.gaana_bajaana	Gaana Bajaana	gaana|bajaana	Gaana|Bajaana	NNP|NNP	PERSON|PERSON	|					
4	2	fb:cell.radhey	Radhey	radhey	radhey	NN	O						
4	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
4	4	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
5	0	fb:cell.2011	2011	2011	2011	CD	DATE	2011	2011.0	2011-xx-xx			
5	1	fb:cell.hudugaru	Hudugaru	hudugaru	Hudugaru	NNP	PERSON						
5	2	fb:cell.gayithri	Gayithri	gayithri	Gayithri	NNP	PERSON						
5	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
5	4	fb:cell.nominated_filmfare_award_for_best_actress_kannada	Nominated, Filmfare Award for Best Actress – Kannada	nominated|,|filmfare|award|for|best|actress|--|kannada	nominate|,|Filmfare|award|for|best|actress|--|Kannada	VBN|,|NNP|NN|IN|JJS|NN|:|NNP	O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|LOCATION	||||||||				Nominated|Filmfare Award for Best Actress – Kannada	fb:part.nominated|fb:part.filmfare_award_for_best_actress_kannada
6	0	fb:cell.2012	2012	2012	2012	CD	DATE	2012	2012.0	2012-xx-xx			
6	1	fb:cell.alemari	Alemari	alemari	Alemari	NNP	PERSON						
6	2	fb:cell.neeli	Neeli	neeli	neelus	NNS	LOCATION						
6	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
6	4	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
7	0	fb:cell.2012	2012	2012	2012	CD	DATE	2012	2012.0	2012-xx-xx			
7	1	fb:cell.breaking_news	Breaking News	breaking|news	break|news	VBG|NNS	O|O	|					
7	2	fb:cell.shraddha	Shraddha	shraddha	shraddha	NN	PERSON						
7	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
7	4	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
8	0	fb:cell.2012	2012	2012	2012	CD	DATE	2012	2012.0	2012-xx-xx			
8	1	fb:cell.addhuri	Addhuri	addhuri	Addhuri	NNP	O						
8	2	fb:cell.poorna	Poorna	poorna	Poorna	NNP	LOCATION						
8	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
8	4	fb:cell.udaya_award_for_best_actress_nominated_siima_award_for_best_actress_nominated_filmfare_award_for_best_actress_kannada	Udaya Award for Best Actress\nNominated — SIIMA Award for Best Actress\nNominated — Filmfare Award for Best Actress – Kannada	udaya|award|for|best|actress|nominated|--|siima|award|for|best|actress|nominated|--|filmfare|award|for|best|actress|--|kannada	Udaya|award|for|best|actress|nominate|--|SIIMA|award|for|best|actress|nominate|--|Filmfare|award|for|best|actress|--|Kannada	NNP|NN|IN|JJS|NN|VBN|:|NNP|NN|IN|JJS|NN|VBN|:|NNP|NN|IN|JJS|NN|:|NNP	O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|LOCATION	||||||||||||||||||||				Udaya Award for Best Actress|Nominated — SIIMA Award for Best Actress|Nominated — Filmfare Award for Best Actress – Kannada	fb:part.udaya_award_for_best_actress|fb:part.nominated_siima_award_for_best_actress|fb:part.nominated_filmfare_award_for_best_actress_kannada
9	0	fb:cell.2012	2012	2012	2012	CD	DATE	2012	2012.0	2012-xx-xx			
9	1	fb:cell.18th_cross	18th Cross	18th|cross	18th|cross	JJ|NN	ORDINAL|O	18.0|	18.0				
9	2	fb:cell.punya	Punya	punya	punya	NN	LOCATION						
9	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
9	4	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
10	0	fb:cell.2012	2012	2012	2012	CD	DATE	2012	2012.0	2012-xx-xx			
10	1	fb:cell.sagar	Sagar	sagar	sagar	FW	LOCATION						
10	2	fb:cell.kajal	Kajal	kajal	Kajal	NNP	PERSON						
10	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
10	4	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
11	0	fb:cell.2012	2012	2012	2012	CD	DATE	2012	2012.0	2012-xx-xx			
11	1	fb:cell.drama	Drama	drama	drama	NN	O						
11	2	fb:cell.nandini	Nandini	nandini	Nandini	NNP	PERSON						
11	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
11	4	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
12	0	fb:cell.2013	2013	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2013	2013.0	2013-xx-xx			
12	1	fb:cell.kaddipudi	Kaddipudi	kaddipudi	Kaddipudi	NNP	LOCATION						
12	2	fb:cell.uma	Uma	uma	uma	NN	PERSON						
12	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
12	4	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
13	0	fb:cell.2013	2013	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2013	2013.0	2013-xx-xx			
13	1	fb:cell.dilwala	Dilwala	dilwala	Dilwala	NNP	PERSON						
13	2	fb:cell.preethi	Preethi	preethi	Preethi	NNP	O						
13	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
13	4	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
14	0	fb:cell.2013	2013	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2013	2013.0	2013-xx-xx			
14	1	fb:cell.bahaddoor	Bahaddoor	bahaddoor	Bahaddoor	NNP	O						
14	2	fb:cell.anjali	Anjali	anjali	Anjali	NNP	PERSON						
14	3	fb:cell.kannada	Kannada	kannada	Kannada	NNP	LOCATION						
14	4	fb:cell.filming	Filming	filming	film	VBG	O					Filming	fb:part.filming
15	0	fb:cell.2014	2014	2014	2014	CD	DATE	2014	2014.0	2014-xx-xx			
15	1	fb:cell.mr_mrs_ramachari	Mr. & Mrs. Ramachari	mr.|&|mrs.|ramachari	Mr.|&|Mrs.|Ramachari	NNP|CC|NNP|NNP	O|O|O|PERSON	|||					
15	2	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
15	3	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
15	4	fb:cell.announced	Announced	announced	announced	JJ	O					Announced	fb:part.announced
16	0	fb:cell.2014	2014	2014	2014	CD	DATE	2014	2014.0	2014-xx-xx			
16	1	fb:cell.endendigu	Endendigu	endendigu	endendigu	NN	MISC						
16	2	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
16	3	fb:cell.null											fb:part.null
16	4	fb:cell.filming	Filming	filming	film	VBG	O					Filming	fb:part.filming
