row	col	id	content	tokens	lemmaTokens	posTags	nerTags	nerValues	number	date	num2	list	listId
-1	0	fb:row.row.date	Date	date	date	NN	O						
-1	1	fb:row.row.label	Label	label	label	NN	O						
-1	2	fb:row.row.format	Format	format	format	NN	O						
-1	3	fb:row.row.country	Country	country	country	NN	O						
-1	4	fb:row.row.catalog	Catalog	catalog	catalog	NN	O						
-1	5	fb:row.row.notes	Notes	notes	note	NNS	O						
0	0	fb:cell.november_10_1969	November 10, 1969	november|10|,|1969	November|10|,|1969	NNP|CD|,|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE|DATE	1969-11-10|1969-11-10|1969-11-10|1969-11-10	101969.0	1969-11-10		November 10|1969	fb:part.november_10|fb:part.1969
0	1	fb:cell.columbia	Columbia	columbia	Columbia	NNP	LOCATION					Columbia	fb:part.columbia
0	2	fb:cell.lp	LP	lp	lp	NN	O						
0	3	fb:cell.us	US	us	US	NNP	LOCATION						
0	4	fb:cell.cs_9942	CS 9942	cs|9942	CS|9942	NNP|CD	O|DATE	|9942	9942.0				
0	5	fb:cell.original_release	Original release.	original|release|.	original|release|.	JJ|NN|.	O|O|O	||					
1	0	fb:cell.january_16_1970	January 16, 1970	january|16|,|1970	January|16|,|1970	NNP|CD|,|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE|DATE	1970-01-16|1970-01-16|1970-01-16|1970-01-16	161970.0	1970-01-16		January 16|1970	fb:part.january_16|fb:part.1970
1	1	fb:cell.cbs	CBS	cbs	CBS	NNP	O					CBS	fb:part.cbs
1	2	fb:cell.lp	LP	lp	lp	NN	O						
1	3	fb:cell.uk	UK	uk	UK	NNP	LOCATION						
1	4	fb:cell.s_63795	S 63795	s|63795	s|63795	NN|CD	O|NUMBER	|63795.0	63795.0				
1	5	fb:cell.original_release	Original release.	original|release|.	original|release|.	JJ|NN|.	O|O|O	||					
2	0	fb:cell.1982	1982	1982	1982	CD	DATE	1982	1982.0	1982-xx-xx		1982	fb:part.1982
2	1	fb:cell.embassy	Embassy	embassy	Embassy	NNP	O					Embassy	fb:part.embassy
2	2	fb:cell.lp	LP	lp	lp	NN	O						
2	3	fb:cell.uk	UK	uk	UK	NNP	LOCATION						
2	4	fb:cell.emb_31956	EMB 31956	emb|31956	EMB|31956	NNP|CD	O|NUMBER	|31956.0	31956.0				
2	5	fb:cell.null											
3	0	fb:cell.1989	1989	1989	1989	CD	DATE	1989	1989.0	1989-xx-xx		1989	fb:part.1989
3	1	fb:cell.columbia	Columbia	columbia	Columbia	NNP	LOCATION					Columbia	fb:part.columbia
3	2	fb:cell.cd	CD	cd	CD	NNP	O						
3	3	fb:cell.us	US	us	US	NNP	LOCATION						
3	4	fb:cell.ck_9942	CK 9942	ck|9942	CK|9942	NNP|CD	O|NUMBER	|9942.0	9942.0				
3	5	fb:cell.original_cd_release	Original CD release.	original|cd|release|.	original|cd|release|.	JJ|NN|NN|.	O|O|O|O	|||					
4	0	fb:cell.march_25_1997	March 25, 1997	march|25|,|1997	March|25|,|1997	NNP|CD|,|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE|DATE	1997-03-25|1997-03-25|1997-03-25|1997-03-25	251997.0	1997-03-25		March 25|1997	fb:part.march_25|fb:part.1997
4	1	fb:cell.columbia_legacy	Columbia/Legacy	columbia\\/legacy	Columbia\\/Legacy	NNP	O					Columbia|Legacy	fb:part.columbia|fb:part.legacy
4	2	fb:cell.cd	CD	cd	CD	NNP	O						
4	3	fb:cell.us	US	us	US	NNP	LOCATION						
4	4	fb:cell.ck_65114	CK 65114	ck|65114	ck|65114	NN|CD	O|NUMBER	|65114.0	65114.0				
4	5	fb:cell.reissue_containing_seven_bonus_tracks_and_the_remastered_stereo_album	Reissue containing seven bonus tracks and the remastered stereo album.	reissue|containing|seven|bonus|tracks|and|the|remastered|stereo|album|.	reissue|contain|seven|bonus|track|and|the|remastered|stereo|album|.	NN|VBG|CD|NN|NNS|CC|DT|JJ|NN|NN|.	MISC|O|NUMBER|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O	||7.0||||||||					
5	0	fb:cell.march_25_1997	March 25, 1997	march|25|,|1997	March|25|,|1997	NNP|CD|,|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE|DATE	1997-03-25|1997-03-25|1997-03-25|1997-03-25	251997.0	1997-03-25		March 25|1997	fb:part.march_25|fb:part.1997
5	1	fb:cell.columbia_legacy	Columbia/Legacy	columbia\\/legacy	Columbia\\/Legacy	NNP	O					Columbia|Legacy	fb:part.columbia|fb:part.legacy
5	2	fb:cell.cd	CD	cd	CD	NNP	O						
5	3	fb:cell.uk	UK	uk	UK	NNP	LOCATION						
5	4	fb:cell.col_486754	COL 486754	col|486754	col|486754	NN|CD	O|NUMBER	|486754.0	486754.0				
5	5	fb:cell.reissue_containing_seven_bonus_tracks_and_the_remastered_stereo_album	Reissue containing seven bonus tracks and the remastered stereo album.	reissue|containing|seven|bonus|tracks|and|the|remastered|stereo|album|.	reissue|contain|seven|bonus|track|and|the|remastered|stereo|album|.	NN|VBG|CD|NN|NNS|CC|DT|JJ|NN|NN|.	MISC|O|NUMBER|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O	||7.0||||||||					
6	0	fb:cell.2003	2003	2003	2003	CD	DATE	2003	2003.0	2003-xx-xx		2003	fb:part.2003
6	1	fb:cell.sony	Sony	sony	Sony	NNP	ORGANIZATION					Sony	fb:part.sony
6	2	fb:cell.cd	CD	cd	CD	NNP	O						
6	3	fb:cell.japan	Japan	japan	Japan	NNP	LOCATION						
6	4	fb:cell.mhcp_102	MHCP-102	mhcp-102	mhcp-102	NN	O		102.0				
6	5	fb:cell.reissue_containing_seven_bonus_tracks_and_the_remastered_album_in_a_replica_lp_sleeve	Reissue containing seven bonus tracks and the remastered album in a replica LP sleeve.	reissue|containing|seven|bonus|tracks|and|the|remastered|album|in|a|replica|lp|sleeve|.	reissue|contain|seven|bonus|track|and|the|remaster|album|in|a|replica|lp|sleeve|.	NN|VBG|CD|NN|NNS|CC|DT|VBN|NN|IN|DT|NN|NN|NN|.	MISC|O|NUMBER|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O|O	||7.0||||||||||||					
