row	col	id	content	tokens	lemmaTokens	posTags	nerTags	nerValues	number	date	num2	list	listId
-1	0	fb:row.row.season	Season	season	season	NN	O						
-1	1	fb:row.row.division_one	Division One	division|one	Division|one	NNP|CD	O|NUMBER	|1.0					
-1	2	fb:row.row.division_two	Division Two	division|two	Division|two	NNP|CD	O|NUMBER	|2.0					
-1	3	fb:row.row.division_three	Division Three	division|three	Division|three	NNP|CD	O|NUMBER	|3.0					
0	0	fb:cell.1983_84	1983–84	1983|--|84	1983|--|84	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1983||84.0	1983.0		84.0		
0	1	fb:cell.whitehawk	Whitehawk	whitehawk	Whitehawk	NNP	O						
0	2	fb:cell.portfield	Portfield	portfield	portfield	NN	LOCATION						
0	3	fb:cell.east_preston	East Preston	east|preston	East|Preston	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
1	0	fb:cell.1984_85	1984–85	1984|--|85	1984|--|85	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1984||85.0	1984.0		85.0		
1	1	fb:cell.steyning_town	Steyning Town	steyning|town	Steyning|Town	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
1	2	fb:cell.shoreham	Shoreham	shoreham	Shoreham	NNP	LOCATION						
1	3	fb:cell.oakwood	Oakwood	oakwood	Oakwood	NNP	LOCATION						
2	0	fb:cell.1985_86	1985–86	1985|--|86	1985|--|86	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1985||86.0	1985.0		86.0		
2	1	fb:cell.steyning_town	Steyning Town	steyning|town	Steyning|Town	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
2	2	fb:cell.wick	Wick	wick	Wick	NNP	O						
2	3	fb:cell.seaford_town	Seaford Town	seaford|town	Seaford|Town	NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION	|					
3	0	fb:cell.1986_87	1986–87	1986|--|87	1986|--|87	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1986||87.0	1986.0		87.0		
3	1	fb:cell.arundel	Arundel	arundel	Arundel	NNP	LOCATION						
3	2	fb:cell.pagham	Pagham	pagham	pagham	NN	LOCATION						
3	3	fb:cell.langney_sports	Langney Sports	langney|sports	Langney|Sports	NNP|NNPS	O|O	|					
4	0	fb:cell.1987_88	1987–88	1987|--|88	1987|--|88	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1987||88.0	1987.0		88.0		
4	1	fb:cell.pagham	Pagham	pagham	pagham	NN	LOCATION						
4	2	fb:cell.langney_sports	Langney Sports	langney|sports	Langney|Sports	NNP|NNPS	O|O	|					
4	3	fb:cell.midway	Midway	midway	Midway	NNP	O						
5	0	fb:cell.1988_89	1988–89	1988|--|89	1988|--|89	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1988||89.0	1988.0		89.0		
5	1	fb:cell.pagham	Pagham	pagham	pagham	NN	LOCATION						
5	2	fb:cell.seaford_town	Seaford Town	seaford|town	Seaford|Town	NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION	|					
5	3	fb:cell.saltdean_united	Saltdean United	saltdean|united	saltdean|United	JJ|NNP	O|O	|					
6	0	fb:cell.1989_90	1989–90	1989|--|90	1989|--|90	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1989||90.0	1989.0		90.0		
6	1	fb:cell.wick	Wick	wick	Wick	NNP	O						
6	2	fb:cell.bexhill_town	Bexhill Town	bexhill|town	Bexhill|Town	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
6	3	fb:cell.worthing_united	Worthing United	worthing|united	worthing|United	JJ|NNP	O|O	|					
7	0	fb:cell.1990_91	1990–91	1990|--|91	1990|--|91	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1990||91.0	1990.0		91.0		
7	1	fb:cell.littlehampton_town	Littlehampton Town	littlehampton|town	Littlehampton|Town	NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION	|					
7	2	fb:cell.newhaven	Newhaven	newhaven	Newhaven	NNP	LOCATION						
7	3	fb:cell.ifield	Ifield	ifield	ifield	NN	O						
8	0	fb:cell.1991_92	1991–92	1991|--|92	1991|--|92	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1991||92.0	1991.0		92.0		
8	1	fb:cell.peacehaven_telscombe	Peacehaven & Telscombe	peacehaven|&|telscombe	Peacehaven|&|Telscombe	NNP|CC|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
8	2	fb:cell.portfield	Portfield	portfield	portfield	NN	LOCATION						
8	3	fb:cell.hassocks	Hassocks	hassocks	hassock	NNS	O						
9	0	fb:cell.1992_93	1992–93	1992|--|93	1992|--|93	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1992||93.0	1992.0		93.0		
9	1	fb:cell.peacehaven_telscombe	Peacehaven & Telscombe	peacehaven|&|telscombe	Peacehaven|&|Telscombe	NNP|CC|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
9	2	fb:cell.crowborough_athletic	Crowborough Athletic	crowborough|athletic	Crowborough|Athletic	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
9	3	fb:cell.withdean	Withdean	withdean	withdean	JJ	MISC						
10	0	fb:cell.1993_94	1993–94	1993|--|94	1993|--|94	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1993||94.0	1993.0		94.0		
10	1	fb:cell.wick	Wick	wick	Wick	NNP	O						
10	2	fb:cell.shoreham	Shoreham	shoreham	Shoreham	NNP	LOCATION						
10	3	fb:cell.bosham	Bosham	bosham	bosham	NN	LOCATION						
11	0	fb:cell.1994_95	1994–95	1994|--|95	1994|--|95	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1994||95.0	1994.0		95.0		
11	1	fb:cell.peacehaven_telscombe	Peacehaven & Telscombe	peacehaven|&|telscombe	Peacehaven|&|Telscombe	NNP|CC|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
11	2	fb:cell.mile_oak	Mile Oak	mile|oak	Mile|Oak	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
11	3	fb:cell.midhurst_easebourne	Midhurst & Easebourne	midhurst|&|easebourne	Midhurst|&|Easebourne	NNP|CC|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
12	0	fb:cell.1995_96	1995–96	1995|--|96	1995|--|96	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1995||96.0	1995.0		96.0		
12	1	fb:cell.peacehaven_telscombe	Peacehaven & Telscombe	peacehaven|&|telscombe	Peacehaven|&|Telscombe	NNP|CC|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
12	2	fb:cell.saltdean_united	Saltdean United	saltdean|united	saltdean|United	JJ|NNP	O|O	|					
12	3	fb:cell.ifield	Ifield	ifield	ifield	NN	O						
13	0	fb:cell.1996_97	1996–97	1996|--|97	1996|--|97	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1996||97.0	1996.0		97.0		
13	1	fb:cell.burgess_hill_town	Burgess Hill Town	burgess|hill|town	Burgess|Hill|Town	NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|LOCATION	||					
13	2	fb:cell.littlehampton_town	Littlehampton Town	littlehampton|town	Littlehampton|Town	NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION	|					
13	3	fb:cell.sidlesham	Sidlesham	sidlesham	Sidlesham	NNP	LOCATION						
14	0	fb:cell.1997_98	1997–98	1997|--|98	1997|--|98	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1997||98.0	1997.0		98.0		
14	1	fb:cell.burgess_hill_town	Burgess Hill Town	burgess|hill|town	Burgess|Hill|Town	NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|LOCATION	||					
14	2	fb:cell.east_preston	East Preston	east|preston	East|Preston	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
14	3	fb:cell.lingfield	Lingfield	lingfield	Lingfield	NNP	LOCATION						
15	0	fb:cell.1998_99	1998–99	1998|--|99	1998|--|99	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	1998||99.0	1998.0		99.0		
15	1	fb:cell.burgess_hill_town	Burgess Hill Town	burgess|hill|town	Burgess|Hill|Town	NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|LOCATION	||					
15	2	fb:cell.sidley_united	Sidley United	sidley|united	Sidley|United	NNP|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	|					
15	3	fb:cell.oving_social_club	Oving Social Club	oving|social|club	Oving|Social|Club	NNP|NNP|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
16	0	fb:cell.1999_2000	1999–2000	1999|--|2000	1999|--|2000	CD|:|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1999|1999|2000	1999.0		2000.0		
16	1	fb:cell.langney_sports	Langney Sports	langney|sports	Langney|Sports	NNP|NNPS	O|O	|					
16	2	fb:cell.sidlesham	Sidlesham	sidlesham	Sidlesham	NNP	LOCATION						
16	3	fb:cell.bosham	Bosham	bosham	bosham	NN	LOCATION						
17	0	fb:cell.2000_01	2000–01	2000|--|01	2000|--|01	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2000||1.0	2000.0		1.0		
17	1	fb:cell.sidley_united	Sidley United	sidley|united	Sidley|United	NNP|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	|					
17	2	fb:cell.southwick	Southwick	southwick	Southwick	NNP	PERSON						
17	3	fb:cell.rye_united	Rye United	rye|united	Rye|United	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
18	0	fb:cell.2001_02	2001–02	2001|--|02	2001|--|02	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2001||2.0	2001.0		2.0		
18	1	fb:cell.burgess_hill_town	Burgess Hill Town	burgess|hill|town	Burgess|Hill|Town	NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|LOCATION	||					
18	2	fb:cell.rye_iden_united	Rye & Iden United	rye|&|iden|united	Rye|&|Iden|United	NNP|CC|NNP|NNP	O|O|O|O	|||					
18	3	fb:cell.pease_pottage_village	Pease Pottage Village	pease|pottage|village	Pease|Pottage|Village	NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|LOCATION	||					
19	0	fb:cell.2002_03	2002–03	2002|--|03	2002|--|03	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2002||3.0	2002.0		3.0		
19	1	fb:cell.burgess_hill_town	Burgess Hill Town	burgess|hill|town	Burgess|Hill|Town	NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|LOCATION	||					
19	2	fb:cell.rye_iden_united	Rye & Iden United	rye|&|iden|united	Rye|&|Iden|United	NNP|CC|NNP|NNP	O|O|O|O	|||					
19	3	fb:cell.midhurst_easebourne	Midhurst & Easebourne	midhurst|&|easebourne	Midhurst|&|Easebourne	NNP|CC|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
20	0	fb:cell.2003_04	2003–04	2003|--|04	2003|--|04	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2003||4.0	2003.0		4.0		
20	1	fb:cell.chichester_city_united	Chichester City United	chichester|city|united	Chichester|City|United	NNP|NNP|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
20	2	fb:cell.littlehampton_town	Littlehampton Town	littlehampton|town	Littlehampton|Town	NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION	|					
20	3	fb:cell.crowborough_athletic	Crowborough Athletic	crowborough|athletic	Crowborough|Athletic	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
21	0	fb:cell.2004_05	2004–05	2004|--|05	2004|--|05	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2004||5.0	2004.0		5.0		
21	1	fb:cell.horsham_y_m_c_a	Horsham Y M C A	horsham|y|m|c|a	Horsham|y|m|c|a	NNP|NN|NN|NN|NN	O|O|O|O|O	||||					
21	2	fb:cell.crowborough_athletic	Crowborough Athletic	crowborough|athletic	Crowborough|Athletic	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
21	3	fb:cell.storrington	Storrington	storrington	Storrington	NNP	PERSON						
22	0	fb:cell.2005_06	2005–06	2005|--|06	2005|--|06	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2005||6.0	2005.0		6.0		
22	1	fb:cell.horsham_y_m_c_a	Horsham Y M C A	horsham|y|m|c|a	Horsham|y|m|c|a	NNP|NN|NN|NN|NN	O|O|O|O|O	||||					
22	2	fb:cell.oakwood	Oakwood	oakwood	Oakwood	NNP	LOCATION						
22	3	fb:cell.peacehaven_telscombe	Peacehaven & Telscombe	peacehaven|&|telscombe	Peacehaven|&|Telscombe	NNP|CC|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
23	0	fb:cell.2006_07	2006–07	2006|--|07	2006|--|07	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2006||7.0	2006.0		7.0		
23	1	fb:cell.eastbourne_town	Eastbourne Town	eastbourne|town	Eastbourne|Town	NNP|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	|					
23	2	fb:cell.pagham	Pagham	pagham	pagham	NN	LOCATION						
23	3	fb:cell.rustington	Rustington	rustington	rustington	NN	PERSON						
24	0	fb:cell.2007_08	2007–08	2007|--|08	2007|--|08	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2007||8.0	2007.0		8.0		
24	1	fb:cell.crowborough_athletic	Crowborough Athletic	crowborough|athletic	Crowborough|Athletic	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
24	2	fb:cell.east_grinstead_town	East Grinstead Town	east|grinstead|town	East|Grinstead|Town	NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O	||					
24	3	fb:cell.loxwood	Loxwood	loxwood	Loxwood	NNP	LOCATION						
25	0	fb:cell.2008_09	2008–09	2008|--|09	2008|--|09	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2008||9.0	2008.0		9.0		
25	1	fb:cell.eastbourne_united_association	Eastbourne United Association	eastbourne|united|association	Eastbourne|United|Association	NNP|NNP|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
25	2	fb:cell.peacehaven_telscombe	Peacehaven & Telscombe	peacehaven|&|telscombe	Peacehaven|&|Telscombe	NNP|CC|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
25	3	fb:cell.clymping	Clymping	clymping	clymp	VBG	O						
26	0	fb:cell.2009_10	2009–10	2009|--|10	2009|--|10	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2009||10.0	2009.0		10.0		
26	1	fb:cell.whitehawk	Whitehawk	whitehawk	Whitehawk	NNP	O						
26	2	fb:cell.rye_united	Rye United	rye|united	Rye|United	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
26	3	fb:cell.bosham	Bosham	bosham	bosham	NN	LOCATION						
27	0	fb:cell.2010_11	2010–11	2010|--|11	2010|--|11	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2010||11.0	2010.0		11.0		
27	1	fb:cell.crawley_down	Crawley Down	crawley|down	Crawley|Down	NNP|NNP	PERSON|O	|					
27	2	fb:cell.a_f_c_uckfield	A.F.C. Uckfield	a.f.c.|uckfield	A.F.C.|Uckfield	NNP|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	|					
27	3	fb:cell.dorking_wanderers	Dorking Wanderers	dorking|wanderers	Dorking|Wanderers	NNP|NNPS	O|O	|					
28	0	fb:cell.2011_12	2011–12	2011|--|12	2011|--|12	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2011||12.0	2011.0		12.0		
28	1	fb:cell.three_bridges	Three Bridges	three|bridges	three|Bridges	CD|NNPS	NUMBER|O	3.0|					
28	2	fb:cell.east_preston	East Preston	east|preston	East|Preston	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
28	3	fb:cell.newhaven	Newhaven	newhaven	Newhaven	NNP	LOCATION						
29	0	fb:cell.2012_13	2012–13	2012|--|13	2012|--|13	CD|:|CD	DATE|O|NUMBER	2012||13.0	2012.0		13.0		
29	1	fb:cell.peacehaven_telscombe	Peacehaven & Telscombe	peacehaven|&|telscombe	Peacehaven|&|Telscombe	NNP|CC|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||					
29	2	fb:cell.littlehampton_town	Littlehampton Town	littlehampton|town	Littlehampton|Town	NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION	|					
29	3	fb:cell.sidlesham	Sidlesham	sidlesham	Sidlesham	NNP	LOCATION						
