row	col	id	content	tokens	lemmaTokens	posTags	nerTags	nerValues	number	date	num2	list	listId
-1	0	fb:row.row.name	Name	name	name	VB	O						
-1	1	fb:row.row.status	Status	status	status	NN	O						
-1	2	fb:row.row.population	Population	population	Population	NNP	O						
-1	3	fb:row.row.district	District	district	District	NNP	O						
-1	4	fb:row.row.former_local_authority	Former local authority	former|local|authority	former|local|authority	JJ|JJ|NN	O|O|O	||					
0	0	fb:cell.cronton	Cronton	cronton	cronton	NN	LOCATION						
0	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
0	2	fb:cell.1_379	1,379	1,379	1,379	CD	NUMBER	1379.0	1379.0				
0	3	fb:cell.knowsley	Knowsley	knowsley	Knowsley	NNP	LOCATION						
0	4	fb:cell.whiston_rural_district	Whiston\nRural District	whiston|rural|district	Whiston|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|O	||				Whiston|Rural District	fb:part.whiston|fb:part.rural_district
1	0	fb:cell.halewood	Halewood	halewood	Halewood	NNP	O						
1	1	fb:cell.town	Town	town	town	NN	O						
1	2	fb:cell.20_309	20,309	20,309	20,309	CD	NUMBER	20309.0	20309.0				
1	3	fb:cell.knowsley	Knowsley	knowsley	Knowsley	NNP	LOCATION						
1	4	fb:cell.whiston_rural_district	Whiston\nRural District	whiston|rural|district	Whiston|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|O	||				Whiston|Rural District	fb:part.whiston|fb:part.rural_district
2	0	fb:cell.huyton_with_roby	Huyton with Roby	huyton|with|roby	huyton|with|Roby	NN|IN|NNP	PERSON|O|PERSON	||					
2	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
2	2	fb:cell.49_859	49,859	49,859	49,859	CD	NUMBER	49859.0	49859.0				
2	3	fb:cell.knowsley	Knowsley	knowsley	Knowsley	NNP	LOCATION						
2	4	fb:cell.huyton_with_roby_urban_district	Huyton with Roby\nUrban District	huyton|with|roby|urban|district	huyton|with|Roby|Urban|District	NN|IN|NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|PERSON|O|O	||||				Huyton with Roby|Urban District	fb:part.huyton_with_roby|fb:part.urban_district
3	0	fb:cell.kirkby	Kirkby	kirkby	Kirkby	NNP	PERSON						
3	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
3	2	fb:cell.40_374	40,374	40,374	40,374	CD	NUMBER	40374.0	40374.0				
3	3	fb:cell.knowsley	Knowsley	knowsley	Knowsley	NNP	LOCATION						
3	4	fb:cell.kirkby_urban_district	Kirkby\nUrban District	kirkby|urban|district	Kirkby|Urban|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O	||				Kirkby|Urban District	fb:part.kirkby|fb:part.urban_district
4	0	fb:cell.knowsley	Knowsley	knowsley	Knowsley	NNP	LOCATION						
4	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
4	2	fb:cell.11_343	11,343	11,343	11,343	CD	NUMBER	11343.0	11343.0				
4	3	fb:cell.knowsley	Knowsley	knowsley	Knowsley	NNP	LOCATION						
4	4	fb:cell.whiston_rural_district	Whiston\nRural District	whiston|rural|district	Whiston|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|O	||				Whiston|Rural District	fb:part.whiston|fb:part.rural_district
5	0	fb:cell.prescot	Prescot	prescot	Prescot	NNP	PERSON						
5	1	fb:cell.town	Town	town	town	NN	O						
5	2	fb:cell.11_184	11,184	11,184	11,184	CD	NUMBER	11184.0	11184.0				
5	3	fb:cell.knowsley	Knowsley	knowsley	Knowsley	NNP	LOCATION						
5	4	fb:cell.prescot_urban_district	Prescot\nUrban District	prescot|urban|district	Prescot|Urban|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O	||				Prescot|Urban District	fb:part.prescot|fb:part.urban_district
6	0	fb:cell.tarbock	Tarbock	tarbock	tarbock	NN	PERSON						
6	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
6	2	fb:cell.2_382	2,382	2,382	2,382	CD	NUMBER	2382.0	2382.0				
6	3	fb:cell.knowsley	Knowsley	knowsley	Knowsley	NNP	LOCATION						
6	4	fb:cell.whiston_rural_district	Whiston\nRural District	whiston|rural|district	Whiston|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|O	||				Whiston|Rural District	fb:part.whiston|fb:part.rural_district
7	0	fb:cell.whiston	Whiston	whiston	Whiston	NNP	PERSON						
7	1	fb:cell.town	Town	town	town	NN	O						
7	2	fb:cell.13_629	13,629	13,629	13,629	CD	NUMBER	13629.0	13629.0				
7	3	fb:cell.knowsley	Knowsley	knowsley	Knowsley	NNP	LOCATION						
7	4	fb:cell.whiston_rural_district	Whiston\nRural District	whiston|rural|district	Whiston|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|O	||				Whiston|Rural District	fb:part.whiston|fb:part.rural_district
8	0	fb:cell.liverpool	Liverpool	liverpool	Liverpool	NNP	LOCATION						
8	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
8	2	fb:cell.439_473	439,473	439,473	439,473	CD	NUMBER	439473.0	439473.0				
8	3	fb:cell.liverpool	Liverpool	liverpool	Liverpool	NNP	LOCATION						
8	4	fb:cell.liverpool_county_borough	Liverpool\nCounty Borough	liverpool|county|borough	Liverpool|County|Borough	NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|LOCATION	||				Liverpool|County Borough	fb:part.liverpool|fb:part.county_borough
9	0	fb:cell.aintree_village	Aintree Village	aintree|village	Aintree|Village	NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION	|					
9	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
9	2	fb:cell.7_126	7,126	7,126	7,126	CD	NUMBER	7126.0	7126.0				
9	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
9	4	fb:cell.west_lancashire_rural_district	West Lancashire\nRural District	west|lancashire|rural|district	West|Lancashire|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O|O	|||				West Lancashire|Rural District	fb:part.west_lancashire|fb:part.rural_district
10	0	fb:cell.bootle	Bootle	bootle	Bootle	NNP	PERSON						
10	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
10	2	fb:cell.59_011	59,011	59,011	59,011	CD	NUMBER	59011.0	59011.0				
10	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
10	4	fb:cell.bootle_county_borough	Bootle\nCounty Borough	bootle|county|borough	Bootle|County|Borough	NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|LOCATION	||				Bootle|County Borough	fb:part.bootle|fb:part.county_borough
11	0	fb:cell.crosby	Crosby	crosby	Crosby	NNP	LOCATION						
11	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
11	2	fb:cell.45_872	45,872	45,872	45,872	CD	NUMBER	45872.0	45872.0				
11	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
11	4	fb:cell.crosby_municipal_borough	Crosby\nMunicipal Borough	crosby|municipal|borough	Crosby|Municipal|Borough	NNP|NNP|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||				Crosby|Municipal Borough	fb:part.crosby|fb:part.municipal_borough
12	0	fb:cell.formby	Formby	formby	Formby	NNP	PERSON						
12	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
12	2	fb:cell.23_586	23,586	23,586	23,586	CD	NUMBER	23586.0	23586.0				
12	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
12	4	fb:cell.formby_urban_district	Formby\nUrban District	formby|urban|district	Formby|Urban|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O	||				Formby|Urban District	fb:part.formby|fb:part.urban_district
13	0	fb:cell.hightown	Hightown	hightown	hightown	JJ	O						
13	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
13	2	fb:cell.2_247	2,247	2,247	2,247	CD	NUMBER	2247.0	2247.0				
13	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
13	4	fb:cell.crosby_municipal_borough	Crosby\nMunicipal Borough	crosby|municipal|borough	Crosby|Municipal|Borough	NNP|NNP|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||				Crosby|Municipal Borough	fb:part.crosby|fb:part.municipal_borough
14	0	fb:cell.ince_blundell	Ince Blundell	ince|blundell	Ince|Blundell	NNP|NNP	O|PERSON	|					
14	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
14	2	fb:cell.518	518	518	518	CD	NUMBER	518.0	518.0				
14	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
14	4	fb:cell.west_lancashire_rural_district	West Lancashire\nRural District	west|lancashire|rural|district	West|Lancashire|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O|O	|||				West Lancashire|Rural District	fb:part.west_lancashire|fb:part.rural_district
15	0	fb:cell.litherland	Litherland	litherland	Litherland	NNP	PERSON						
15	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
15	2	fb:cell.18_629	18,629	18,629	18,629	CD	NUMBER	18629.0	18629.0				
15	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
15	4	fb:cell.litherland_urban_district	Litherland\nUrban District	litherland|urban|district	Litherland|Urban|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O	||				Litherland|Urban District	fb:part.litherland|fb:part.urban_district
16	0	fb:cell.little_altcar	Little Altcar	little|altcar	little|altcar	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
16	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
16	2	fb:cell.892	892	892	892	CD	NUMBER	892.0	892.0				
16	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
16	4	fb:cell.west_lancashire_rural_district	West Lancashire\nRural District	west|lancashire|rural|district	West|Lancashire|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O|O	|||				West Lancashire|Rural District	fb:part.west_lancashire|fb:part.rural_district
17	0	fb:cell.lydiate	Lydiate	lydiate	Lydiate	NNP	O						
17	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
17	2	fb:cell.6_672	6,672	6,672	6,672	CD	NUMBER	6672.0	6672.0				
17	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
17	4	fb:cell.west_lancashire_rural_district	West Lancashire\nRural District	west|lancashire|rural|district	West|Lancashire|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O|O	|||				West Lancashire|Rural District	fb:part.west_lancashire|fb:part.rural_district
18	0	fb:cell.maghull	Maghull	maghull	maghull	NN	O						
18	1	fb:cell.town	Town	town	town	NN	O						
18	2	fb:cell.22_225	22,225	22,225	22,225	CD	NUMBER	22225.0	22225.0				
18	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
18	4	fb:cell.west_lancashire_rural_district	West Lancashire\nRural District	west|lancashire|rural|district	West|Lancashire|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O|O	|||				West Lancashire|Rural District	fb:part.west_lancashire|fb:part.rural_district
19	0	fb:cell.melling	Melling	melling	mell	VBG	PERSON						
19	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
19	2	fb:cell.2_810	2,810	2,810	2,810	CD	NUMBER	2810.0	2810.0				
19	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
19	4	fb:cell.west_lancashire_rural_district	West Lancashire\nRural District	west|lancashire|rural|district	West|Lancashire|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O|O	|||				West Lancashire|Rural District	fb:part.west_lancashire|fb:part.rural_district
20	0	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
20	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
20	2	fb:cell.772	772	772	772	CD	NUMBER	772.0	772.0				
20	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
20	4	fb:cell.west_lancashire_rural_district	West Lancashire\nRural District	west|lancashire|rural|district	West|Lancashire|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O|O	|||				West Lancashire|Rural District	fb:part.west_lancashire|fb:part.rural_district
21	0	fb:cell.southport	Southport	southport	Southport	NNP	LOCATION						
21	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
21	2	fb:cell.90_336	90,336	90,336	90,336	CD	NUMBER	90336.0	90336.0				
21	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
21	4	fb:cell.southport_county_borough	Southport\nCounty Borough	southport|county|borough	Southport|County|Borough	NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|LOCATION	||				Southport|County Borough	fb:part.southport|fb:part.county_borough
22	0	fb:cell.thornton	Thornton	thornton	Thornton	NNP	PERSON						
22	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
22	2	fb:cell.2_262	2,262	2,262	2,262	CD	NUMBER	2262.0	2262.0				
22	3	fb:cell.sefton	Sefton	sefton	Sefton	NNP	PERSON						
22	4	fb:cell.west_lancashire_rural_district	West Lancashire\nRural District	west|lancashire|rural|district	West|Lancashire|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O|O	|||				West Lancashire|Rural District	fb:part.west_lancashire|fb:part.rural_district
23	0	fb:cell.billinge_chapel_end	Billinge Chapel End	billinge|chapel|end	Billinge|chapel|end	NNP|NN|NN	MISC|MISC|MISC	||					
23	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
23	2	fb:cell.6_554	6,554	6,554	6,554	CD	NUMBER	6554.0	6554.0				
23	3	fb:cell.st_helens	St Helens	st|helens	St|Helens	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
23	4	fb:cell.billinge_and_winstanley_urban_district	Billinge and Winstanley\nUrban District	billinge|and|winstanley|urban|district	Billinge|and|Winstanley|Urban|District	NNP|CC|NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|PERSON|O|O	||||				Billinge and Winstanley|Urban District	fb:part.billinge_and_winstanley|fb:part.urban_district
24	0	fb:cell.bold	Bold	bold	bold	JJ	O						
24	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
24	2	fb:cell.2_283	2,283	2,283	2,283	CD	NUMBER	2283.0	2283.0				
24	3	fb:cell.st_helens	St Helens	st|helens	St|Helens	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
24	4	fb:cell.whiston_rural_district	Whiston\nRural District	whiston|rural|district	Whiston|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|O	||				Whiston|Rural District	fb:part.whiston|fb:part.rural_district
25	0	fb:cell.eccleston	Eccleston	eccleston	Eccleston	NNP	PERSON						
25	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
25	2	fb:cell.10_528	10,528	10,528	10,528	CD	NUMBER	10528.0	10528.0				
25	3	fb:cell.st_helens	St Helens	st|helens	St|Helens	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
25	4	fb:cell.whiston_rural_district	Whiston\nRural District	whiston|rural|district	Whiston|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|O	||				Whiston|Rural District	fb:part.whiston|fb:part.rural_district
26	0	fb:cell.haydock	Haydock	haydock	Haydock	NNP	PERSON						
26	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
26	2	fb:cell.15_684	15,684	15,684	15,684	CD	NUMBER	15684.0	15684.0				
26	3	fb:cell.st_helens	St Helens	st|helens	St|Helens	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
26	4	fb:cell.haydock_urban_district	Haydock\nUrban District	haydock|urban|district	Haydock|Urban|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O	||				Haydock|Urban District	fb:part.haydock|fb:part.urban_district
27	0	fb:cell.newton_le_willows	Newton le Willows	newton|le|willows	Newton|le|Willows	NNP|DT|NNP	LOCATION|O|O	||					
27	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
27	2	fb:cell.21_418	21,418	21,418	21,418	CD	NUMBER	21418.0	21418.0				
27	3	fb:cell.st_helens	St Helens	st|helens	St|Helens	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
27	4	fb:cell.newton_le_willows_urban_district	Newton le Willows\nUrban District	newton|le|willows|urban|district	Newton|le|Willows|Urban|District	NNP|DT|NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|O|O|O|O	||||				Newton le Willows|Urban District	fb:part.newton_le_willows|fb:part.urban_district
28	0	fb:cell.rainford	Rainford	rainford	rainford	NN	PERSON						
28	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
28	2	fb:cell.8_344	8,344	8,344	8,344	CD	NUMBER	8344.0	8344.0				
28	3	fb:cell.st_helens	St Helens	st|helens	St|Helens	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
28	4	fb:cell.rainford_urban_district	Rainford\nUrban District	rainford|urban|district	Rainford|Urban|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O	||				Rainford|Urban District	fb:part.rainford|fb:part.urban_district
29	0	fb:cell.rainhill	Rainhill	rainhill	rainhill	NN	PERSON						
29	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
29	2	fb:cell.11_913	11,913	11,913	11,913	CD	NUMBER	11913.0	11913.0				
29	3	fb:cell.st_helens	St Helens	st|helens	St|Helens	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
29	4	fb:cell.whiston_rural_district	Whiston\nRural District	whiston|rural|district	Whiston|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|O	||				Whiston|Rural District	fb:part.whiston|fb:part.rural_district
30	0	fb:cell.seneley_green	Seneley Green	seneley|green	Seneley|Green	NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION	|					
30	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
30	2	fb:cell.6_163	6,163	6,163	6,163	CD	NUMBER	6163.0	6163.0				
30	3	fb:cell.st_helens	St Helens	st|helens	St|Helens	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
30	4	fb:cell.ashton_in_makerfield_urban_district	Ashton in Makerfield\nUrban District	ashton|in|makerfield|urban|district	Ashton|in|Makerfield|Urban|District	NNP|IN|NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|O|O|O	||||				Ashton in Makerfield|Urban District	fb:part.ashton_in_makerfield|fb:part.urban_district
31	0	fb:cell.st_helens	St Helens	st|helens	St|Helens	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
31	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
31	2	fb:cell.91_414	91,414	91,414	91,414	CD	NUMBER	91414.0	91414.0				
31	3	fb:cell.st_helens	St Helens	st|helens	St|Helens	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
31	4	fb:cell.st_helens_county_borough	St Helens\nCounty Borough	st|helens|county|borough	St|Helens|County|Borough	NNP|NNP|NNP|NNP	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	|||				St Helens|County Borough	fb:part.st_helens|fb:part.county_borough
32	0	fb:cell.windle	Windle	windle	Windle	NNP	PERSON						
32	1	fb:cell.civil_parish	Civil parish	civil|parish	civil|parish	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
32	2	fb:cell.2_542	2,542	2,542	2,542	CD	NUMBER	2542.0	2542.0				
32	3	fb:cell.st_helens	St Helens	st|helens	St|Helens	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
32	4	fb:cell.whiston_rural_district	Whiston\nRural District	whiston|rural|district	Whiston|Rural|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	PERSON|O|O	||				Whiston|Rural District	fb:part.whiston|fb:part.rural_district
33	0	fb:cell.bebington	Bebington	bebington	Bebington	NNP	PERSON						
33	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
33	2	fb:cell.58_226	58,226	58,226	58,226	CD	NUMBER	58226.0	58226.0				
33	3	fb:cell.wirral	Wirral	wirral	wirral	JJ	O						
33	4	fb:cell.bebington_municipal_borough	Bebington\nMunicipal Borough	bebington|municipal|borough	Bebington|Municipal|Borough	NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O	||				Bebington|Municipal Borough	fb:part.bebington|fb:part.municipal_borough
34	0	fb:cell.birkenhead	Birkenhead	birkenhead	Birkenhead	NNP	PERSON						
34	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
34	2	fb:cell.103_206	103,206	103,206	103,206	CD	NUMBER	103206.0	103206.0				
34	3	fb:cell.wirral	Wirral	wirral	wirral	JJ	O						
34	4	fb:cell.birkenhead_county_borough	Birkenhead\nCounty Borough	birkenhead|county|borough	Birkenhead|County|Borough	NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|LOCATION	||				Birkenhead|County Borough	fb:part.birkenhead|fb:part.county_borough
35	0	fb:cell.heswall	Heswall	heswall	Heswall	NNP	PERSON						
35	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
35	2	fb:cell.29_977	29,977	29,977	29,977	CD	NUMBER	29977.0	29977.0				
35	3	fb:cell.wirral	Wirral	wirral	wirral	JJ	O						
35	4	fb:cell.wirral_urban_district	Wirral\nUrban District	wirral|urban|district	wirral|Urban|District	JJ|NNP|NNP	O|O|O	||				Wirral|Urban District	fb:part.wirral|fb:part.urban_district
36	0	fb:cell.hoylake	Hoylake	hoylake	Hoylake	NNP	LOCATION						
36	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
36	2	fb:cell.35_655	35,655	35,655	35,655	CD	NUMBER	35655.0	35655.0				
36	3	fb:cell.wirral	Wirral	wirral	wirral	JJ	O						
36	4	fb:cell.hoylake_urban_district	Hoylake\nUrban District	hoylake|urban|district	Hoylake|Urban|District	NNP|NNP|NNP	O|O|O	||				Hoylake|Urban District	fb:part.hoylake|fb:part.urban_district
37	0	fb:cell.wallasey	Wallasey	wallasey	Wallasey	NNP	LOCATION						
37	1	fb:cell.unparished_area	Unparished area	unparished|area	unparished|area	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
37	2	fb:cell.84_348	84,348	84,348	84,348	CD	NUMBER	84348.0	84348.0				
37	3	fb:cell.wirral	Wirral	wirral	wirral	JJ	O						
37	4	fb:cell.wallasey_county_borough	Wallasey\nCounty Borough	wallasey|county|borough	Wallasey|County|Borough	NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|LOCATION	||				Wallasey|County Borough	fb:part.wallasey|fb:part.county_borough
