row	col	id	content	tokens	lemmaTokens	posTags	nerTags	nerValues	number	date	num2	list	listId
-1	0	fb:row.row.ecclesiastical_jurisdictions	Ecclesiastical Jurisdictions	ecclesiastical|jurisdictions	ecclesiastical|jurisdiction	JJ|NNS	O|O	|					
-1	1	fb:row.row.latin_name	Latin name	latin|name	latin|name	JJ|NN	O|O	|					
-1	2	fb:row.row.type	Type	type	type	NN	O						
-1	3	fb:row.row.rite	Rite	rite	rite	NN	O						
-1	4	fb:row.row.ecclesiastical_province	Ecclesiastical Province	ecclesiastical|province	ecclesiastical|Province	JJ|NNP	O|O	|					
-1	5	fb:row.row.established	Established	established	establish	VBN	O						
-1	6	fb:row.row.area_km2	Area (km2)	area|-lrb-|km2|-rrb-	area|-lrb-|km2|-rrb-	NN|-LRB-|NN|-RRB-	O|O|O|O	|||					
0	0	fb:cell.benguela	Benguela	benguela	Benguela	NNP	LOCATION						
0	1	fb:cell.benguelensis	Benguelensis	benguelensis	Benguelensis	NNP	PERSON						
0	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
0	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
0	4	fb:cell.huambo	Huambo	huambo	Huambo	NNP	LOCATION						
0	5	fb:cell.6_june_1970	6 June 1970	6|june|1970	6|June|1970	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1970-06-06|1970-06-06|1970-06-06	6.0	1970-06-06	1970.0		
0	6	fb:cell.49_920	49,920	49,920	49,920	CD	NUMBER	49920.0	49920.0				
1	0	fb:cell.cabinda	Cabinda	cabinda	Cabinda	NNP	LOCATION						
1	1	fb:cell.cabindanus	Cabindanus	cabindanus	Cabindanus	NNP	O						
1	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
1	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
1	4	fb:cell.luanda	Luanda	luanda	Luanda	NNP	LOCATION						
1	5	fb:cell.2_july_1984	2 July 1984	2|july|1984	2|July|1984	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1984-07-02|1984-07-02|1984-07-02	2.0	1984-07-02	1984.0		
1	6	fb:cell.7_120	7,120	7,120	7,120	CD	NUMBER	7120.0	7120.0				
2	0	fb:cell.caxito	Caxito	caxito	Caxito	NNP	LOCATION						
2	1	fb:cell.caxitonsis	Caxitonsis	caxitonsis	Caxitonsis	NNP	O						
2	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
2	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
2	4	fb:cell.luanda	Luanda	luanda	Luanda	NNP	LOCATION						
2	5	fb:cell.6_june_2007	6 June 2007	6|june|2007	6|June|2007	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	2007-06-06|2007-06-06|2007-06-06	6.0	2007-06-06	2007.0		
2	6	fb:cell.25_133	25,133	25,133	25,133	CD	NUMBER	25133.0	25133.0				
3	0	fb:cell.dundo	Dundo	dundo	Dundo	NNP	LOCATION						
3	1	fb:cell.dundensis	Dundensis	dundensis	Dundensis	NNP	PERSON						
3	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
3	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
3	4	fb:cell.luanda	Luanda	luanda	Luanda	NNP	LOCATION						
3	5	fb:cell.9_november_2001	9 November 2001	9|november|2001	9|November|2001	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	2001-11-09|2001-11-09|2001-11-09	9.0	2001-11-09	2001.0		
3	6	fb:cell.103_130	103,130	103,130	103,130	CD	NUMBER	103130.0	103130.0				
4	0	fb:cell.huambo	Huambo	huambo	Huambo	NNP	LOCATION						
4	1	fb:cell.huambensis	Huambensis	huambensis	Huambensis	NNP	PERSON						
4	2	fb:cell.metropolitan_archdiocese	Metropolitan Archdiocese	metropolitan|archdiocese	Metropolitan|Archdiocese	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
4	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
4	4	fb:cell.huambo	Huambo	huambo	Huambo	NNP	LOCATION						
4	5	fb:cell.4_september_1940	4 September 1940	4|september|1940	4|September|1940	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1940-09-04|1940-09-04|1940-09-04	4.0	1940-09-04	1940.0		
4	6	fb:cell.29_500	29,500	29,500	29,500	CD	NUMBER	29500.0	29500.0				
5	0	fb:cell.kwito_bie	Kwito-Bié	kwito|bié	Kwito|Bié	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
5	1	fb:cell.kvitobiensis	Kvitobiensis	kvitobiensis	Kvitobiensis	NNP	PERSON						
5	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
5	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
5	4	fb:cell.huambo	Huambo	huambo	Huambo	NNP	LOCATION						
5	5	fb:cell.4_september_1940	4 September 1940	4|september|1940	4|September|1940	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1940-09-04|1940-09-04|1940-09-04	4.0	1940-09-04	1940.0		
5	6	fb:cell.71_000	71,000	71,000	71,000	CD	NUMBER	71000.0	71000.0				
6	0	fb:cell.luanda	Luanda	luanda	Luanda	NNP	LOCATION						
6	1	fb:cell.luandensis	Luandensis	luandensis	Luandensis	NNP	PERSON						
6	2	fb:cell.metropolitan_archdiocese	Metropolitan Archdiocese	metropolitan|archdiocese	Metropolitan|Archdiocese	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
6	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
6	4	fb:cell.luanda	Luanda	luanda	Luanda	NNP	LOCATION						
6	5	fb:cell.1596	1596	1596	1596	CD	DATE	1596	1596.0	1596-xx-xx			
6	6	fb:cell.1_074	1,074	1,074	1,074	CD	NUMBER	1074.0	1074.0				
7	0	fb:cell.lubango	Lubango	lubango	Lubango	NNP	LOCATION						
7	1	fb:cell.lubangensis	Lubangensis	lubangensis	Lubangensis	NNP	PERSON						
7	2	fb:cell.metropolitan_archdiocese	Metropolitan Archdiocese	metropolitan|archdiocese	Metropolitan|Archdiocese	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
7	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
7	4	fb:cell.lubango	Lubango	lubango	Lubango	NNP	LOCATION						
7	5	fb:cell.27_july_1955	27 July 1955	27|july|1955	27|July|1955	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1955-07-27|1955-07-27|1955-07-27	27.0	1955-07-27	1955.0		
7	6	fb:cell.118_000	118,000	118,000	118,000	CD	NUMBER	118000.0	118000.0				
8	0	fb:cell.lwena	Lwena	lwena	Lwena	NNP	LOCATION						
8	1	fb:cell.lvenanus	Lvenanus	lvenanus	lvenanus	NN	O						
8	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
8	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
8	4	fb:cell.saurimo	Saurimo	saurimo	Saurimo	NNP	LOCATION						
8	5	fb:cell.1_july_1963	1 July 1963	1|july|1963	1|July|1963	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1963-07-01|1963-07-01|1963-07-01	1.0	1963-07-01	1963.0		
8	6	fb:cell.199_786	199,786	199,786	199,786	CD	NUMBER	199786.0	199786.0				
9	0	fb:cell.malanje	Malanje	malanje	Malanje	NNP	LOCATION						
9	1	fb:cell.malaniensis	Malaniensis	malaniensis	malaniensis	NN	O						
9	2	fb:cell.metropolitan_archdiocese	Metropolitan Archdiocese	metropolitan|archdiocese	Metropolitan|Archdiocese	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
9	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
9	4	fb:cell.malanje	Malanje	malanje	Malanje	NNP	LOCATION						
9	5	fb:cell.25_november_1957	25 November 1957	25|november|1957	25|November|1957	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1957-11-25|1957-11-25|1957-11-25	25.0	1957-11-25	1957.0		
9	6	fb:cell.107_000	107,000	107,000	107,000	CD	NUMBER	107000.0	107000.0				
10	0	fb:cell.mbanza_congo	Mbanza Congo	mbanza|congo	Mbanza|Congo	NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION	|					
10	1	fb:cell.mbanzacongensis	Mbanzacongensis	mbanzacongensis	Mbanzacongensis	NNP	O						
10	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
10	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
10	4	fb:cell.luanda	Luanda	luanda	Luanda	NNP	LOCATION						
10	5	fb:cell.7_november_1984	7 November 1984	7|november|1984	7|November|1984	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1984-11-07|1984-11-07|1984-11-07	7.0	1984-11-07	1984.0		
10	6	fb:cell.39_459	39,459	39,459	39,459	CD	NUMBER	39459.0	39459.0				
11	0	fb:cell.menongue	Menongue	menongue	Menongue	NNP	LOCATION						
11	1	fb:cell.menonguensis	Menonguensis	menonguensis	menonguensis	NN	O						
11	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
11	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
11	4	fb:cell.lubango	Lubango	lubango	Lubango	NNP	LOCATION						
11	5	fb:cell.10_august_1975	10 August 1975	10|august|1975	10|August|1975	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1975-08-10|1975-08-10|1975-08-10	10.0	1975-08-10	1975.0		
11	6	fb:cell.213_309	213,309	213,309	213,309	CD	NUMBER	213309.0	213309.0				
12	0	fb:cell.namibe	Namibe	namibe	Namibe	NNP	LOCATION						
12	1	fb:cell.namibanus	Namibanus	namibanus	namibanus	NN	O						
12	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
12	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
12	4	fb:cell.lubango	Lubango	lubango	Lubango	NNP	LOCATION						
12	5	fb:cell.21_march_2009	21 March 2009	21|march|2009	21|March|2009	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	2009-03-21|2009-03-21|2009-03-21	21.0	2009-03-21	2009.0		
12	6	fb:cell.57_097	57,097	57,097	57,097	CD	NUMBER	57097.0	57097.0				
13	0	fb:cell.ndalatando	Ndalatando	ndalatando	Ndalatando	NNP	LOCATION						
13	1	fb:cell.ndalatandensis	Ndalatandensis	ndalatandensis	Ndalatandensis	NNP	O						
13	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
13	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
13	4	fb:cell.malanje	Malanje	malanje	Malanje	NNP	LOCATION						
13	5	fb:cell.26_march_1990	26 March 1990	26|march|1990	26|March|1990	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1990-03-26|1990-03-26|1990-03-26	26.0	1990-03-26	1990.0		
13	6	fb:cell.20_159	20,159	20,159	20,159	CD	NUMBER	20159.0	20159.0				
14	0	fb:cell.ondjiva	Ondjiva	ondjiva	ondjiva	NN	O						
14	1	fb:cell.ondiivanus	Ondiivanus	ondiivanus	ondiivanus	NN	O						
14	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
14	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
14	4	fb:cell.lubango	Lubango	lubango	Lubango	NNP	LOCATION						
14	5	fb:cell.10_august_1975	10 August 1975	10|august|1975	10|August|1975	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1975-08-10|1975-08-10|1975-08-10	10.0	1975-08-10	1975.0		
14	6	fb:cell.83_900	83,900	83,900	83,900	CD	NUMBER	83900.0	83900.0				
15	0	fb:cell.saurimo	Saurimo	saurimo	Saurimo	NNP	LOCATION						
15	1	fb:cell.saurimoensis	Saurimoënsis	saurimoënsis	saurimoënsis	FW	O						
15	2	fb:cell.metropolitan_archdiocese	Metropolitan Archdiocese	metropolitan|archdiocese	Metropolitan|Archdiocese	NNP|NNP	O|O	|					
15	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
15	4	fb:cell.saurimo	Saurimo	saurimo	Saurimo	NNP	LOCATION						
15	5	fb:cell.10_august_1975	10 August 1975	10|august|1975	10|August|1975	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1975-08-10|1975-08-10|1975-08-10	10.0	1975-08-10	1975.0		
15	6	fb:cell.77_000	77,000	77,000	77,000	CD	NUMBER	77000.0	77000.0				
16	0	fb:cell.sumbe	Sumbe	sumbe	Sumbe	NNP	LOCATION						
16	1	fb:cell.sumbensis	Sumbensis	sumbensis	Sumbensis	NNP	O						
16	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
16	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
16	4	fb:cell.luanda	Luanda	luanda	Luanda	NNP	LOCATION						
16	5	fb:cell.10_august_1975	10 August 1975	10|august|1975	10|August|1975	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1975-08-10|1975-08-10|1975-08-10	10.0	1975-08-10	1975.0		
16	6	fb:cell.60_000	60,000	60,000	60,000	CD	NUMBER	60000.0	60000.0				
17	0	fb:cell.uije	Uíje	uíje	uíje	NN	O						
17	1	fb:cell.uiiensis	Uiiensis	uiiensis	Uiiensis	NNP	O						
17	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
17	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
17	4	fb:cell.luanda	Luanda	luanda	Luanda	NNP	LOCATION						
17	5	fb:cell.14_march_1967	14 March 1967	14|march|1967	14|March|1967	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	1967-03-14|1967-03-14|1967-03-14	14.0	1967-03-14	1967.0		
17	6	fb:cell.63_530	63,530	63,530	63,530	CD	NUMBER	63530.0	63530.0				
18	0	fb:cell.viana	Viana	viana	Viana	NNP	PERSON						
18	1	fb:cell.viananensis	Viananensis	viananensis	Viananensis	NNP	PERSON						
18	2	fb:cell.diocese	Diocese	diocese	Diocese	NNP	O						
18	3	fb:cell.roman	Roman	roman	Roman	NNP	MISC						
18	4	fb:cell.luanda	Luanda	luanda	Luanda	NNP	LOCATION						
18	5	fb:cell.6_june_2007	6 June 2007	6|june|2007	6|June|2007	CD|NNP|CD	DATE|DATE|DATE	2007-06-06|2007-06-06|2007-06-06	6.0	2007-06-06	2007.0		
18	6	fb:cell.17_206	17,206	17,206	17,206	CD	NUMBER	17206.0	17206.0				
